<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on edelgrace.me</title>
    <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on edelgrace.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 01:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Guitar: Week 1</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/music/learning-the-guitar-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 01:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/music/learning-the-guitar-week-1/</guid>
      <description>I have been following Justin Guitar&amp;#8216;s lesson plans for learning the guitar.
This week I went through the first 15 beginner&amp;#8217;s course lessons, BC-101 to BC-115. I learned the basics of choosing a guitar, posture, etc. In terms of actually playing, I learned the D chord, A chord, and E chord. The first two chords were incredibly &amp;#8220;easy.&amp;#8221; The chord that really stumped me was the E chord. I could not press down on the strings hard enough so that it didn&amp;#8217;t sound muted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Listened To: Electra Heart by Marina and the Diamonds</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/music/i-listened-to-electra-heart-by-marina-and-the-diamonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/music/i-listened-to-electra-heart-by-marina-and-the-diamonds/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Lyrics relating to suicide is mentioned in this post.
Another disclaimer: I&amp;#8217;m not good at writing reviews but I do like expressing my opinions. This is in no way a professional review but rather how I personally feel about this album.
I know Marina and the Diamonds&amp;#8217; album Electra Heart is one of her personally least favourite works but I like it a lot. Many people think Electra Heart represents an alter-ego but it&amp;#8217;s rather a personality that Marina holds in disdain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bought Some New Music!</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/10/bought-some-new-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 03:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/10/bought-some-new-music/</guid>
      <description>Lately I&amp;#8217;ve been using Spotify a lot. I only ever use it when I&amp;#8217;m at my computer. When I&amp;#8217;m on the go, I turn to my trusty iPod classic. Since I use the free version of Spotify (now that I have a job, I can&amp;#8217;t say that I&amp;#8217;m a broke college student anymore but I can say that I&amp;#8217;m still cheap), being able to choose what I listen to is a must and Spotify mobile doesn&amp;#8217;t have that ability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #1</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/06/random-tumblr-posts-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/06/random-tumblr-posts-1/</guid>
      <description>Ugh I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;#8217;m sorry. I&amp;#8217;ll try to make this as painless as possible.
 I had a dream where I literally just lived out my entire day, down to sitting in lecture being bored and taking notes.
You don’t even know how disappointed I am when I woke up knowing that I had to do it all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Approaching this Blog &amp; R.I.P hide</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/05/on-approaching-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 16:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/05/on-approaching-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Suicide content warning.
My philosophy with this blog has always been to approach in a very casual and informal way. I was inspired by a blog to do so, but I don&amp;#8217;t quite remember what site it was exactly (I&amp;#8217;m tempted to say it was 6birds, but I&amp;#8217;m not entirely sure). I try to have this mindset whenever I need to write a blog post. Even so, I don&amp;#8217;t entirely feel free in writing whatever I want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Started to Play TCGs Again</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/04/i-started-to-play-tcgs-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 05:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/04/i-started-to-play-tcgs-again/</guid>
      <description>Since I gave up Tumblr for Lent, I realized how much free time I had on my hands without Tumblr. I decided, why not get back into TCGs? And so I did.
TCG stands for &amp;#8220;Trading Card Game.&amp;#8221; There are TCGs around the Internet that you can join as long as you yourself have a bit of space on the Internet. The goal of the game is basically to collect all the cards that are available in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musical Finds</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/03/musical-finds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 06:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/03/musical-finds/</guid>
      <description>Man, lately I&amp;#8217;ve just been scouring the Internet (okay, YouTube) for new music. I&amp;#8217;m so hungry for new music! Anyway, here are my findings.
Buhar Jerreau
These guys are at the top of my list at the moment. They&amp;#8217;re a hip-hop/rap group of three guys from Kazakhstan. According to translations of their lyrics, I find them to be extremely talented at song writing. I really am in love with the beats of their songs (I don&amp;#8217;t know rap lingo&amp;#8230;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tagalog and Translated English Lyrics: “Panginoon” by Yeng Constantino</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/01/tagalog-and-translated-english-lyrics-panginoon-by-yeng-constantino/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 00:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/01/tagalog-and-translated-english-lyrics-panginoon-by-yeng-constantino/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: I&amp;#8217;m not fluent in Tagalog but I am Filipino. English is my first language. This translation is improvised in some parts and relied heavily on Google Translate and my (very limited) existing knowledge of the language.
I love Yeng Constantino (Filipino singer). I put this song at the very front of my Filofax to remind me of two things: to be proud of being Filipino and to keep my mind focused on God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But Seriously Though. AJ is perfect.</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2013/11/but-seriously-though-aj-is-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 19:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2013/11/but-seriously-though-aj-is-perfect/</guid>
      <description>AJ reminds me of Kemal. As much as I&amp;#8217;d hate to say it, that&amp;#8217;s the number one reason why I find AJ so attractive. He&amp;#8217;s like the Korean version of Kemal. Also, I&amp;#8217;d rather fangirl over AJ than be madly crushing on a guy who probably thinks I&amp;#8217;m an idiot and who I haven&amp;#8217;t seen in almost a year.
However, I saw Kemal on campus a while ago and I realized how much they don&amp;#8217;t really look like each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But Seriously Though. U-KISS</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2013/11/but-seriously-though-u-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 03:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2013/11/but-seriously-though-u-kiss/</guid>
      <description>Okay I admittedly watch too many videos on YouTube when I should be doing school things but I really like looking for videos of U-KISS. I find it to be so embarrassing that I am a fan. I have to watch metal1 music videos afterwards to regain my manliness get rid of that sickly sweet aftertaste in my mouth that I get when I look, hear, or even think about at U-KISS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving L’Arc~en~Ciel</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2013/11/loving-larcenciel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2013/11/loving-larcenciel/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s no secret to many people that L&amp;#8217;Arc~en~Ciel is my favourite band. No, not one of my favourite bands, but my favourite band. Previously, my favourite band had been Green Day, from about grade four to junior high school. They were a great band for me at the time but they didn&amp;#8217;t have a timeless feel to them. After listening to L&amp;#8217;Arc~en~Ciel, I quickly dumped them.
When I was in junior high I even wrote an essay about how L&amp;#8217;Arc~en~Ciel had impacted my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Afterman: Ascension (A Reaction)</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2012/10/the-afterman-ascension-a-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 02:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2012/10/the-afterman-ascension-a-reaction/</guid>
      <description>Track Listing
 The Hollow Key Entity Extraction I: Domino The Destitute The Afterman Mothers of Men Goodnight, Fair Lady Key Entity Extraction II: Holly Wood The Cracked Key Entity Extraction III: Vic The Butcher Key Entity Extraction IV: Evagaria The Faithful Subtraction  WARNING: Reaction blog posts are probably not blog posts at all but rather, a mass wall of incoherent garble of text. This probably belongs on something like Tumblr but it was too long and you know Tumblr kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Songs I’ve Been Playing on Repeat</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2012/09/three-songs-ive-been-playing-on-repeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2012/09/three-songs-ive-been-playing-on-repeat/</guid>
      <description>These past two months or so have been great for new music. G-Dragon&amp;#8217;s comeback and news of Coheed and Cambria&amp;#8217;s new album. So many good things are happening! Lately, there has been three songs that I&amp;#8217;ve been playing over and over again.

A gif made by vitadolce-moderato.   The first one worth mentioning is G-Dragon&amp;#8217;s new ballad, That XX{.external}. For those who don&amp;#8217;t know, G-Dragon is a South Korean artist part of the boy group BIG BANG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Discoveries #1</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2012/08/youtube-discoveries-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 21:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2012/08/youtube-discoveries-1/</guid>
      <description>Listening to: Sunadokei by L&amp;#8217;Arc~en~Ciel
Fave song atm: Somebody to Love by CLUBSODA
Fave musician(s) atm: Uhh&amp;#8230; I actually have no idea
 Just so you all know, I waded through 7000+ forums posts to find all the YouTube links I wanted to post here. Then I realized I could have used the search function. OTL Anyway, on to the post. Warning, there&amp;#8217;s a lot here. I don&amp;#8217;t know if you&amp;#8217;d want to read it all but yeah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIR EN GREY WHY</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2012/07/dir-en-grey-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 10:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2012/07/dir-en-grey-why/</guid>
      <description>A couple days ago, the Diru fandom on Tumblr was freaking out. I checked the DIR EN GREY tag just to be in the loop. Lo and behold, I see screenshots of this. I immediately went to the official website{.external} and there it was. The background was slowly fading in and out with different pictures and the timer slowly ticked away.
First, I freaked out. I went on Twitter, saw @DEG_CANADA&amp;#8217;s tweet about the countdown and key smashed like there was no tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>