<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on edelgrace.me</title>
    <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on edelgrace.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 23:48:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Tinkering with My Productivity System</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/forever-tinkering-with-my-productivity-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 23:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/forever-tinkering-with-my-productivity-system/</guid>
      <description>I follow the blog baty.net in which Jack Baty continuously finds new tools and new ways to improve his productivity. While I usually scoff at people who are always changing things up, I will admit that I am the exact same way. It would be great to just stick to something tried and true and never have to think about changing but there is just so much out there that it&amp;#8217;s hard for me to resist the temptation to not try everything I can see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m a Little Behind</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I was behind on my granny squares for my temperature blanket. If you don&amp;#8217;t know, temperature blankets consist of one square a day and each square represents the temperature of that day. Thankfully, it&amp;#8217;s easy to catch up with temperature blankets! Even though I&amp;#8217;m caught up with the squares, I still haven&amp;#8217;t woven the ends in yet nor have I joined them. Eek!
Last week I was babysitting my little cousin and he was playing with my yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STASH Lounge Moving and Other Outings</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yesterday opened up at their new location across the street. I dragged my brother along with me to the opening.
It was absolutely lovely! They had a DJ play some music in the background, a coffee bar, and a table of yummy sweets in the back. They even had door prizes, which I suspect I didn&amp;#8217;t win anything from but that&amp;#8217;s totally okay.
In terms of the space, it&amp;#8217;s great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Crocheting on a Road Trip</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 15:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to Drumheller with the family. Up to this point I haven&amp;#8217;t had a chance to go on a long road trip with my crochet. I started this ripple afghan a couple of days ago with Bernat Blanket Stripes yarn. This blanket is intended for my cousins&amp;#8217;s newborn son. I guess he isn&amp;#8217;t quite so newborn now but every baby could use a blanket regardless! I actually restarted this blanket once or twice but I finally got the hang of it while on this trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stampede Food</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/stampede-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/stampede-food/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, Stampede is synonymous with food for me. Stampede means free breakfasts for a week. Usually these breakfasts consists of pancakes and sausages. We ended up going to six of these breakfasts. Some of them were worth it, some of them weren&amp;#8217;t. One of them actually ended up being $250 because my brother got fined for forgetting to validate his train ticket on the way to a breakfast. But still, a lot of pancakey goodness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Out in Pre-Stampede Rush</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</guid>
      <description>I went to the first pancake breakfast of the season with my family the other day. It was close to home which was a great bonus because my dad had the car for work. The breakfast wasn&amp;#8217;t busy at all but maybe being fairly early was a factor. They only served pancakes and sausage patties but they were pretty good! There was also a Tim Hortons truck giving out free coffee and hot chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kits and Knits</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/kits-and-knits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/kits-and-knits/</guid>
      <description>Last week was the end of final exams and on my last exam, I decided to take a well deserved day out. In celebration of Canada Day, Tim Hortons was bringing back Roll Up the Rim for a time. I&amp;#8217;m trying to cut down on my coffee but I decided to get at least one cup, just to try my luck. Turns out that my luck isn&amp;#8217;t that so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Before 25: Update #1</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25-update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 01:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25-update-1/</guid>
      <description>I took a little break during the month of May. My mental health was honestly at an all time low and I found myself having a hard time picking myself back up to get motivated to actually do things. Since I am around 6 months into my 22nd year of living, I thought it would be a good time to pause and reflect how I&amp;#8217;m doing with my 25 before 25.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #16</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/book-blogger-hop-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/book-blogger-hop-16/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Would you stop reading a book if an element of the plot strongly clashed with your personal beliefs, or would you continue reading until you finished the book?
 I would definitely finish the book. At least, that&amp;#8217;s what I think and hope I would do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at Cafe Blanca</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/an-hour-at-cafe-blanca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 09:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/an-hour-at-cafe-blanca/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;#8217;s a cool hip place at the edge of Calgary&amp;#8217;s Chinatown and across Eau Claire Market called Cafe Blanca. They&amp;#8217;re most known for their Siphon coffee which I unfortunately did not remember to try. Instead, I ordered a plain normal latte and a cheesecake.

Now, I&amp;#8217;m not cheesecake expert but I&amp;#8217;m definitely a cheesecake lover. I got myself a mint chocolate cheesecake. It was extremely delicious. It was a little more cake than I prefer (the base was an actual chocolate cake and yes, cake, not brownie) and not as much cheese as I&amp;#8217;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paint Nite Calgary at Yuk Yuk’s Comedy Club</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/paint-nite-at-yuk-yuks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/paint-nite-at-yuk-yuks/</guid>
      <description>One of the interns at my workplace suggested going painting as an activity that we could all do together. It seemed fun so we decided to give it a try! Paint Nite is a series of painting events held at bars, each session hosted by different people.
That day we went to Yuk Yuk&amp;#8217;s Comedy Club which is a few minutes walk from Victoria Park Stampede. We were really confused about the food since there was no (or incorrect) information on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art, Food, and Good Old Bowling</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/art-food-and-good-old-bowling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 09:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/art-food-and-good-old-bowling/</guid>
      <description>At the company where I&amp;#8217;m doing an internship right now offered all the interns the opportunity to go to their downtown location and give us a tour of all the art. It seems a little weird to give art tours in an office environment but once we stepped into the building, it made sense. There was art on every single floor of the building (of which there are over ten floors) and almost every single wall has a piece of art hanging on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Can I Get Coffee After Five in this City?</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/where-can-i-get-coffee-after-five-in-this-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 05:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/where-can-i-get-coffee-after-five-in-this-city/</guid>
      <description>I found myself in downtown with cancelled plans the other day. I didn&amp;#8217;t have to be home for another two hours so I decided to try a new coffee place. It was around five in the evening. I pulled up Google Maps and searched for coffee.
Scrolling through the list, I found that most of the coffee places closed at 5:00PM or 6:00PM. I needed a place to sit and blog hop for a little bit so that was no good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Joined a Gym</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/i-joined-a-gym/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/i-joined-a-gym/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to do more things in my free time, I decided to join a gym. My original plan was to go to my university gym however since I am on co-op, I no longer have the discounted membership included in my tuition. Instead, I opted for my local Fit4Less. It is an extremely more convenient location, significantly cheaper, and a good &amp;#8220;introductory&amp;#8221; gym for those who are just starting out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #3</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/weekly-drawing-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 02:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/weekly-drawing-3/</guid>
      <description>Last week&amp;#8217;s theme was fantasy. The original picture was a lot more ethereal and pretty. I had to redraw this one because I messed up the background. The background was definitely the hardest part because the original picture relied heavily on colour.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>