<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crochet on edelgrace.me</title>
    <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/crochet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crochet on edelgrace.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 04:45:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/crochet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FO: Candy Print Alpine Nights Beanie</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-candy-print-alpine-nights-beanie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 04:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-candy-print-alpine-nights-beanie/</guid>
      <description>FO stands for &amp;#8220;finished object.&amp;#8221; It is a term used by knitters and crocheters.
 I recently finished a hat that my cousin asked me to make for her daughter. At first I wanted to knit a hat but I decided to crochet it instead. I looked through many different patterns and had trouble finding one that I liked the most. I settled on Alpine Nights because the pattern seemed not only simple but also very pretty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m a Little Behind</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I was behind on my granny squares for my temperature blanket. If you don&amp;#8217;t know, temperature blankets consist of one square a day and each square represents the temperature of that day. Thankfully, it&amp;#8217;s easy to catch up with temperature blankets! Even though I&amp;#8217;m caught up with the squares, I still haven&amp;#8217;t woven the ends in yet nor have I joined them. Eek!
Last week I was babysitting my little cousin and he was playing with my yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Steps Forward, One Step Back</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/two-steps-forward-one-step-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 03:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/two-steps-forward-one-step-back/</guid>
      <description>I finally finished one Bernat Blanket Stripes cake! I am going to move onto cake number two for my afghan ripple blanket. I don&amp;#8217;t really know yet who this blanket will be for. My mom keeps asking me and I can&amp;#8217;t make up my mind. I am pretty happy that I am making progress on this blanket. I might need three cakes for this though and not the two that I have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STASH Lounge Moving and Other Outings</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yesterday opened up at their new location across the street. I dragged my brother along with me to the opening.
It was absolutely lovely! They had a DJ play some music in the background, a coffee bar, and a table of yummy sweets in the back. They even had door prizes, which I suspect I didn&amp;#8217;t win anything from but that&amp;#8217;s totally okay.
In terms of the space, it&amp;#8217;s great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Crocheting on a Road Trip</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 15:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to Drumheller with the family. Up to this point I haven&amp;#8217;t had a chance to go on a long road trip with my crochet. I started this ripple afghan a couple of days ago with Bernat Blanket Stripes yarn. This blanket is intended for my cousins&amp;#8217;s newborn son. I guess he isn&amp;#8217;t quite so newborn now but every baby could use a blanket regardless! I actually restarted this blanket once or twice but I finally got the hang of it while on this trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a Nanodegree at Udacity</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/programming/starting-a-nanodegree-at-udacity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 18:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/programming/starting-a-nanodegree-at-udacity/</guid>
      <description>While I&amp;#8217;m still looking for a job this summer (which is almost halfway over already&amp;#8230; Blah!) I took a cue from Y who started to work on some side projects and I decided to be a little more productive. Since I have a free month of Udacity from the GitHub Student Pack. Udacity is basically an online learning hub where you can take courses that are related to the tech field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #6: My Second Granny Square</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-6-my-second-granny-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 04:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-6-my-second-granny-square/</guid>
      <description>FO means &amp;#8220;finished object&amp;#8221; in crochet and knitter terms. So any completed project is a finished object!
 After making my first granny square, I quickly made my second granny square. Both were made from Loop &amp;amp; Threads yarn of the wool variety. I can&amp;#8217;t remember the exact name of the yarn.
I am not quite sure about the colour choices but they were the colours I had on hand of the same yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winding Yarn Multitasking</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/winding-yarn-multitasking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 10:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/winding-yarn-multitasking/</guid>
      <description>Since I recently started making a temperature blanket. I bought a couple of skeins of yarn (Bernat Premium, they are so soft!) and decided to wind them into balls to make transporting them easier for when/if I&amp;#8217;m on the go. Surprisingly, it takes a while for them to wind up. I thought it was a perfect opportunity to watch some TV shows while doing it.
I decided to finish up watching season 2 of Knights of Sidonia, an anime about a human space colony at war with alien-like creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Out in Pre-Stampede Rush</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</guid>
      <description>I went to the first pancake breakfast of the season with my family the other day. It was close to home which was a great bonus because my dad had the car for work. The breakfast wasn&amp;#8217;t busy at all but maybe being fairly early was a factor. They only served pancakes and sausage patties but they were pretty good! There was also a Tim Hortons truck giving out free coffee and hot chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canada 150 Temperature Blanket: First Colour Change</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/canada-150-temperature-blanket-first-colour-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 22:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/canada-150-temperature-blanket-first-colour-change/</guid>
      <description>A post shared by Edel Altares (@edelgraceme) on Jul 5, 2017 at 3:41pm PDT   Since the beginning of July, I&amp;#8217;ve been recording the highs and lows of the daily temperature through granny squares. The middle colour represents the low of the day and the outer colour represents the high of the day. The first three days of July were roughly the same but the fourth was a little bit cooler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Haul #8: Gina Brown’s First Visit</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-8-gina-browns-first-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-8-gina-browns-first-visit/</guid>
      <description>I went to visit another local yarn store called Gina Brown&amp;#8217;s. I was in the area waiting to meet up with some friends and decided to pop in and check the place out. It&amp;#8217;s way too convenient that this place is a ten minute walk away from a train station.
It&amp;#8217;s a nice store. In the back there&amp;#8217;s a big table available for classes and (I&amp;#8217;m assuming) to just knit or crochet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Haul #7: The Knitting Room First Visit</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-7-the-knitting-room-first-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 07:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-7-the-knitting-room-first-visit/</guid>
      <description>I have been going to the Brentwood Village Mall for the past couple of years now and I have never ever noticed this nice little yarn store before until I started up crochet. The Knitting Room is a small store located in a mall close to my university. I usually go to the mall when I&amp;#8217;m itching to walk somewhere between classes. I decided to finally visit The Knitting Room for the first time and came away with some yarn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooked on Crochet Spring 2017 Swap</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/hooked-on-crochet-spring-2017-swap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 17:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/hooked-on-crochet-spring-2017-swap/</guid>
      <description>Hooked on Crochet is a Discord server that I am a part of. If you don&amp;#8217;t know what Discord is, it is essentially a chat client for gamers. You can create your own &amp;#8220;servers&amp;#8221; or chat rooms for dedicated topics. Hooked on Crochet is (obviously) a group of crocheters. They organized a yarn swap last spring which I took a part of.
My gifter got me a set of hand dyed Alpaca yarn, a llama stitch marker, and a pattern for a unicorn amigurumi!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #5: My First Granny Square</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-5-my-first-granny-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 18:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-5-my-first-granny-square/</guid>
      <description>My previous FO was part of the March National Crochet Month and this one is no different. Except this event is a charity run. This square will be going to a charity to be part of a blanket! Different squares from different people will all be sewn together. I think it&amp;#8217;s a cool joint effort!

It took me a swatch to get the hang of making a granny square. Thankfully the process is straightforward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #4: NatCroMo2017 Mystery Crochet Along</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-4-natcromo2017-mystery-crochet-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 08:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-4-natcromo2017-mystery-crochet-along/</guid>
      <description>March is National Crochet Month. A group on Ravelry holds a series of events during the month to celebrate. One of these events is a mystery crochet along! Basically, the finished product is a mystery and parts of the pattern is slowly released throughout the month.
There were times I fell a little behind the clues but I managed to finish it off! Honestly, I find it a little bit derpy but that&amp;#8217;s part of it&amp;#8217;s charm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>