<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jr High on edelgrace.me</title>
    <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/jr-high/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jr High on edelgrace.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 02:17:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/jr-high/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Parties, Food, School, and . . . Michael Jackson!</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2009/06/lake-parties-food-school-and-michael-jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 02:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2009/06/lake-parties-food-school-and-michael-jackson/</guid>
      <description>Some updates&amp;#8230; Alright, I&amp;#8217;ve got the basic Nav links up. Sadly, I forgot the Affies and Linkage&amp;#8230; links. TT_TT I&amp;#8217;ll fix it later (read the last paragraph). I got my Twitter up, my stats counter, and a new C-BOX! What am I missing? Oh right, actual content! Don&amp;#8217;t worry, I&amp;#8217;m working on it&amp;#8230;
Now back to real life&amp;#8230; Yesterday I went to a party for the end of the year. Okay, it was more like a BBQ but it still counts, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Again!</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2008/04/absolute-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 04:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2008/04/absolute-again/</guid>
      <description>My skool is posted on a band&amp;#8217;s website! That&amp;#8217;s never happened before. In the picture{.external}, the first school listed is my school. It was career day today and the day ended with the Absolute Presentation. I remember the presentation form last year. Last year was better but mainly because the band was better (Colin Lingren is amazing). But apparently the band that came to our school was better in terms of success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Late Pizza</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/12/late-pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 01:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/12/late-pizza/</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day of school for winter break! Yay! We were supposed to have pizza but it never came&amp;#8230; We also watched a movie that I have watched too many times: The Polar Express. Then my camera ran out of batteries after I just took one picture of my friends. It wasn&amp;#8217;t a great day, but I&amp;#8217;m glad it&amp;#8217;s just over.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Bank</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/12/food-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 08:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/12/food-bank/</guid>
      <description>Today, my TA went to the church across the street to help out with the food hampers. Our job was to bring all 200 something boxes from the basement to the main floor. Do you know how hard that is? It was definitely a workout for me. I got my friend pat to help me with over half of my boxes and he calls me lazy. There was this freight elevator, and we had to bring carts full of food with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TA</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/09/ta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2007 05:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/09/ta/</guid>
      <description>Three days ago, I started school, and I found out that we no longer have homerooms. Now we have TA I went to my TA in the band room and found three grade niners there, and I thought I was in the wrong homeroom, but I wasn&amp;#8217;t. Oh and guess who my teacher advisors are? The principal and the vice principal! This is going to be one great year.
I have three of my friends in my TA and I have to stick with my TA Until I finish junior high&amp;#8230; b=Vleh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beauti</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/04/beauti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2007 16:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/04/beauti/</guid>
      <description>Beauti is a pretty good band. Right now, they&amp;#8217;re on tour with this thing called Absolute. They travel all across Canada to high schools. Which really doesn&amp;#8217;t make any sense because I&amp;#8217;m in junior high. Anyway, they played four songs (actually three, but they played one song while the kids went into the gym). I forget what one song was, but the two songs they played was Forever Love, and Don&amp;#8217;t Watch Me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grade Niners</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/01/grade-niners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 23:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2007/01/grade-niners/</guid>
      <description>My locker&amp;#8217;s right next to the band room, and grade niners are constantly standing around my locker. The grade niners like to listen to this guy play the drums every single lunch period. I was opening my locker, and the guy who plays the drums was looking at my locker. They saw my Billie Joe Armstrong poster (which unfortunately does not exist anymore because one of my friends tore it up).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>