<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on edelgrace.me</title>
    <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on edelgrace.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 04:07:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Vegetarian by Han Kang</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 04:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</guid>
      <description>Yeong-hye and her husband are ordinary people. He is an office worker with moderate ambitions and mild manners; she is an uninspired but dutiful wife. The acceptable flatline of their marriage is interrupted when Yeong-hye, seeking a more &amp;#8216;plant-like&amp;#8217; existence, decides to become a vegetarian, prompted by grotesque recurring nightmares. In South Korea, where vegetarianism is almost unheard-of and societal mores are strictly obeyed, Yeong-hye&amp;#8217;s decision is a shocking act of subversion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: God in Pink by Hasan Namir</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-god-in-pink-by-hasan-namir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 22:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-god-in-pink-by-hasan-namir/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Topics of sexuality, religion, and spoilers for the book is mentioned in this blog post.
 A revelatory novel about being queer and Muslim, set in war-torn Iraq in 2003. Ramy is a young gay Iraqi struggling to find a balance between his sexuality, religion, and culture. Ammar is a sheikh whose guidance Ramy seeks, and whose tolerance is tested by his belief in the teachings of the Qur&amp;#8217;an. Full of quiet moments of beauty and raw depictions of violence, God in Pink poignantly captures the anguish and the fortitude of Islamic life in Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #21</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-21/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Name a book that changed your life.
 Busting out the big questions. This is a hard one to answer. I think that I&amp;#8217;m still trying to find it. I have my favourite books but I&amp;#8217;m not sure of their impact on my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #20</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 07:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-20/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you are at a really good point in a book and the phone rings or the door bell rings, do you stop reading or let the phone or door bell go unanswered?
 Honestly, I would get up and check them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Vital Signs by Tessa McWatt</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</guid>
      <description>After thirty years of marriage, producing three now-grown children, Mike and Anna have settled into entrenched domesticity. She is skillful and poised and still beautiful, an instructor of English at the city college. He is a successful graphic artist on the verge of retirement, his awards and ambitions and accomplishments largely behind him. Though the couple’s erotic life has dimmed somewhat, he still considers her ravishing.
But their apparent balance is thrown asunder when Anna breaks the normal silence of their breakfast table with uncontrollable babble about hummingbirds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #19</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 07:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-19/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you organize your blog in terms of what is in your side bar? Do you have categories and defined sections in your side bar?
 At the moment, my side bar is laid out by links to my favourite bloggers, categories, monthly archives, and recent comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Frankenstein by Mary Shelley</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 06:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</guid>
      <description>To many readers, who have perhaps known Frankenstein only at second hand, the original may well come as a surprise. When Mary Shelley began it, she was only eighteen, though she was already Shelley&amp;#8217;s mistress and Byron&amp;#8217;s friend. In her preface she explains how she and Shelley spent part of a wet summer with Byron in Switzerland, amusing themselves by reading and writing ghost stories. Her contribution was Frankenstein, a story about a student of natural philosophy who learns the secret of imparting life to a creature constructed from bones he has collected in charnel-houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #18</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-18/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you could have lunch with any living authors and/or book bloggers, who would you choose and why?
 Oh man, the living restriction is a tough one. If language wasn&amp;#8217;t a barrier, I would definitely have lunch with Haruki Murakami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Nine Island by Jane Alison</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</guid>
      <description>Nine Island is an intimate autobiographical novel, told by J, a woman who lives in a glass tower on one of Miami Beach’s lush Venetian Islands. After decades of disaster with men, she is trying to decide whether to withdraw forever from romantic love. Having just returned to Miami from a monthlong reunion with an old flame, “Sir Gold,” and a visit to her fragile mother, J begins translating Ovid’s magical stories about the transformations caused by Eros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #17</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-17/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do your bookshelves have books ONLY or do you also have bookish items on the shelves?
 I have books, bookish items, and non-bookish items on my shelves. Actually my shelves are in a pretty sorry state. There is a lot of clutter on them and they&amp;#8217;re usually my go to place to put things when I have no idea where to put them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #15</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hope-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hope-15/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 When you feature a book in your posts, do you include a book cover?
 I definitely try my best to do so. It seems a little weird to write a blog post about a book without featuring the cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #14</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-14/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you could meet one author, dead or alive, who would it be? Submitted by Kristin @ Lukten av Trykksverte
 I am in love with the Brontë sisters. Their lives intrigue me a great deal and the sense of mystery surrounding them is too much for me to take at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Birthday of the World and Other Stories by Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</guid>
      <description>For more than four decades, Ursula K. Le Guin has enthralled readers with her imagination, clarity, and moral vision. The recipient of numerous literary prizes, including the National Book Award, the Kafka Award, and five Hugo and five Nebula Awards, this renowned writer has, in each story and novel, created a provocative, ever-evolving universe filled with diverse worlds and rich characters reminiscent of our earthly selves.
Now, in The Birthday of the World, this gifted artist returns to these worlds in eight brilliant short works, including a never-before-published novella, each of which probes the essence of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #13</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-13/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;#8217;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you visit every listed blog in the linky list when you are participating in a meme? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;#8217;s Reviews
 I try to! But I don&amp;#8217;t always manage to do so. I usually do my blog hopping on the train to/from work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Gamelife by Michael Clune</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/books/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</guid>
      <description>You have been awakened.
Floppy disk inserted, computer turned on, a whirring, and then this sentence, followed by a blinking cursor. So begins Suspended, the first computer game to obsess seven-year-old Michael, to worm into his head and change his sense of reality. Thirty years later he will write: &amp;#8220;Computer games have taught me the things you can&amp;#8217;t learn from people.&amp;#8221;
Gamelife is the memoir of a childhood transformed by technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>