<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet on edelgrace.me</title>
    <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet on edelgrace.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 01:48:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.edelgrace.me/categories/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LFTP Fatal Error: Certificate verification</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/10/lftp-fatal-error-certificate-verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/10/lftp-fatal-error-certificate-verification/</guid>
      <description>The error: ~$ git-ftp pull&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; ~$ cd: Fatal error: Certificate verification: certificate common name doesn&amp;rsquo;t match requested host name ‘ftp.mazohyst.org’&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; ~$ mirror: Fatal error: Certificate verification: certificate common name doesn&amp;rsquo;t match requested host name ‘ftp.mazohyst.org’
Solution: Edit ~/.lftp/rc so that it contains set ssl:check-hostname no. What this does is pretty self explanatory. If the hostname in the certificate does not match the hostname you&amp;#8217;re attempting to connect to, it doesn&amp;#8217;t matter because it won&amp;#8217;t check for that in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking of Security</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/06/speaking-of-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 22:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/06/speaking-of-security/</guid>
      <description>My last post was about security by obscurity and I talked a little about trying to implement security techniques into my projects. This is really great timing.
Last week, various online services ran by my university were down. It was really inconvenient not having access to my e-mail but I took it in stride. I figured it was just the servers acting up or malware or something like that. It turns out that my university was dealing with a ransomware attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Years of Blogging</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/02/9-years-of-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 21:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/02/9-years-of-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I know that probably isn&amp;#8217;t a lot compared to other bloggers out there but to me, that&amp;#8217;s mind blowing. 9 years is around 40% of my life and that percentage will only keep on increasing. Assuming that I continue blogging. As long as I can type, I don&amp;#8217;t think I would stop blogging. Sure, my blogging might be extremely sporadic but it&amp;#8217;s still blogging to me.
Actually, I was going through my archive and I read a blog post that was from exactly six years and two days ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comics Aren’t Just Kids Stuff!</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/02/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 01:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2016/02/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</guid>
      <description>I initially started writing this post in 2012. I&amp;#8217;ve been going through and cleaning out my drafts and decided this one was worthy of continuing and actually publishing.
Comics are usually written off as being childish or something only nerds can enjoy. But, I&amp;#8217;m not here to argue whether comics are legitimate literature or not. I&amp;#8217;m here to point out some of my favourite web comics. I don&amp;#8217;t know where it started but I got bored one day and eventually ended up on a web comics site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally Imported Those Old Posts</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2015/09/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 19:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2015/09/finally-imported-those-old-posts/</guid>
      <description>So now that I&amp;#8217;ve moved hosts, I decided to do some spring cleaning (fall cleaning?). Right now, my databases are a mess. I have a lot of databases that aren&amp;#8217;t used and databases that are waiting to be used. I still had my old blog database, back from when Brokenphrases was my main blog. So, I decided to to import all those pages and posts here.
Now my blog post archive is pretty much complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Moved Hosts to Network Panda</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2015/09/i-moved-hosts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 01:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2015/09/i-moved-hosts/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been with Three Words Hosting for a long time now. I can&amp;#8217;t exactly pinpoint how long&amp;#8230; But I still had my first domain while I was with them. I remember when I had to jump from host to host because they kept disappearing. However, when I found Three Words, I felt like I could stay there forever. Honestly, I have nothing but praise for Misaki. She&amp;#8217;s been an outstanding host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transition to Foundation: Successful?</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2015/08/transition-to-foundation-successful/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 17:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2015/08/transition-to-foundation-successful/</guid>
      <description>Okay I&amp;#8217;m so angry, I wrote this entire post out in the &amp;#8220;Quick Draft&amp;#8221; section of my dashboard, clicked &amp;#8220;Save Draft&amp;#8221; and then when I came back, what I wrote was erased. :( This happens a lot but not enough for me to remember to save entries locally before I publish&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;ll try my best to recreate what I just wrote. I&amp;#8217;m still really salty, haha.
In my previous post, I mentioned that I was moving from Bootstrap to Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link Dump #2</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/08/link-dump-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 04:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/08/link-dump-2/</guid>
      <description>I only have one link today, that&amp;#8217;s the blog Altair &amp;amp; Vega.
Altair &amp;amp; Vega is an extremely insightful blog that delves deep into the narrative and art of many popular anime and manga titles. They have a group of multiple authors and while their posts aren&amp;#8217;t regular, when they do show up on my news feed, it&amp;#8217;s a great treat.
I forget how I originally got to this site. I probably stumbled upon it through the post on the anime Hyouka, &amp;#8220;And You Don&amp;#8217;t Doubt Your Own?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #3</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/07/random-tumblr-posts-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 02:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/07/random-tumblr-posts-3/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Implied misogynistic content, alluding to the USBC shootings, and mentions of rape.
I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;#8217;m sorry. I&amp;#8217;ll try to make this as painless as possible. Here are some posts I&amp;#8217;ve made on Tumblr.
 I was listening to an episode of the Internet Box, which was recorded around the time when Andrew got a Tumblr and started stirring the pot with the social justice fan community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Tumblr Posts #1</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/06/random-tumblr-posts-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/06/random-tumblr-posts-1/</guid>
      <description>Ugh I write SO MUCH on Tumblr even though I have a blog sitting here just waiting to be used. I&amp;#8217;m sorry. I&amp;#8217;ll try to make this as painless as possible.
 I had a dream where I literally just lived out my entire day, down to sitting in lecture being bored and taking notes.
You don’t even know how disappointed I am when I woke up knowing that I had to do it all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Approaching this Blog &amp; R.I.P hide</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/05/on-approaching-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 16:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/05/on-approaching-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Suicide content warning.
My philosophy with this blog has always been to approach in a very casual and informal way. I was inspired by a blog to do so, but I don&amp;#8217;t quite remember what site it was exactly (I&amp;#8217;m tempted to say it was 6birds, but I&amp;#8217;m not entirely sure). I try to have this mindset whenever I need to write a blog post. Even so, I don&amp;#8217;t entirely feel free in writing whatever I want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Started to Play TCGs Again</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/04/i-started-to-play-tcgs-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 05:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/04/i-started-to-play-tcgs-again/</guid>
      <description>Since I gave up Tumblr for Lent, I realized how much free time I had on my hands without Tumblr. I decided, why not get back into TCGs? And so I did.
TCG stands for &amp;#8220;Trading Card Game.&amp;#8221; There are TCGs around the Internet that you can join as long as you yourself have a bit of space on the Internet. The goal of the game is basically to collect all the cards that are available in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Monday After is Always the Worst</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/03/the-monday-after-is-always-the-worst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 23:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/03/the-monday-after-is-always-the-worst/</guid>
      <description>The Monday after reading week is always the worst, that is. I told my friend who is from the States that I had reading week and she had no idea what it is. It&amp;#8217;s pretty much a Canadian/Commonwealth countries thing where we get a couple days off in the middle of the semester. I heard from the grapevine that reading week started because mid-semester is a period when too stressed out students tend to commit suicide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brokenphrases is Expiring Soon</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/01/brokenphrases-is-expiring-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 19:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2014/01/brokenphrases-is-expiring-soon/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, you heard that right. It&amp;#8217;s expiring in a couple of months. I&amp;#8217;ve had this domain for almost four years now. That&amp;#8217;s so weird to think about! You can &amp;#8220;see&amp;#8221; Brokenphrases in it&amp;#8217;s first reincarnation by going into the Wayback Archive. Reading those posts make me cringe. And I remember when I actually tried making money off of my posts. LOL. I earned like seven cents writing that one post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Twas the Night Before the Last Final….</title>
      <link>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2013/12/twas-the-night-before-the-last-final/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 05:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.edelgrace.me/2013/12/twas-the-night-before-the-last-final/</guid>
      <description>And all though the house
Not a creature was stirring
Not even a certain university student who should be cramming.
Today was everything but studying. I had the intentions of doing so. I even planned out my day! Then things happened. Those things consist of: music and Ray. I spent most of my day hanging out on Last.fm. Then I went to make a quick tweet about how much I hate recursion, for when I actually decided to crack open my textbook for two seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>